<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get-starteds on Managed IoT Cloud Workshops</title>
    <link>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get-starteds on Managed IoT Cloud Workshops</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/</guid>
      <description>This section will explain why the Managed IoT Cloud platform (MIC) is a powerful tool for managing your IoT infrastructure and why you should consider using it for your projects.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with a quick background about the MIC platform and who operates it to get you oriented.
Telenor Connexion: Platform Development and Commercial offering Telenor Connexion is a branch in the Telenor company with its headquarters in Stockholm, Sweden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why use MIC</title>
      <link>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/why-use-mic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/why-use-mic/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re probably wondering &amp;ldquo;what does MIC has to offer for me?&amp;rdquo;.
There are several components, both known and unknown to most of us, when creating a full-blown IoT infrastructure. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to say &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll just spin up a SQL database and pipe all my data to it&amp;rdquo;, but how will you connect your IoT devices through LoRaWAN / NB-IoT, handle realtime updates, structure a fleet of e.g. 100+ IoT devices and query gigabytes of data stored years ago?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>The Arduino MKR NB 1500 is fully compatible with Telenor Norways Narrow Band IoT (NB-IoT) and LTE CAT M1 networks. In this workshop we&amp;rsquo;ll go through how to provision a device in MIC and how to program the Arduino MKR NB 1500 to send data using the open mda.ee APN over the Telenor NB-IoT network.
Before continuing, make sure that:
 You have access to a valid MIC account (if you are attending an event, an account will be announced for you during the event) or go here to create one:  https://startiot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NB-IoT Architectural Overview</title>
      <link>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/architectural-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://telenorstartiot.github.io/mic-workshops/get-started/architectural-overview/</guid>
      <description>Developers first The Telenor Start IoT initiative has taken a developer first approach and has set up everything you need to get started with NB-IoT development and integrated it with the MIC platform used in the initiative. The next two paragraphs illustrates how this has been done. Feel free to skip reading it, it is just for your information :-)
Telenor LTE architecture and NB-IoT If you just buy NB-IoT/Cat M1 SIM cards you will have to either use the open telenor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>